resellrightsmastery.com 2017-12-16

# Edmund Loh's Resell Rights Mastery - Privacy Policy

**Resell Rights Mastery  
****_Privacy Policy_**

**ResellRightsMastery.com** values and respects the privacy of its visitors and members. This policy, known as the Privacy Policy, details the type of information we collect from you, and what we do with that information. The privacy policy shall be accepted as part of the Terms of Service.

**_Personal Information_**

**ResellRightsMastery.com** collects your Username, First Name, Last Name, and E-mail address when you first sign up with the site. We also ask for additional, optional information through our registration form, including but not limited to your mailing address.

**_Method of Information Collecting_**

**ResellRightsMastery.com** uses "cookies" to store and track visitor information. A cookie is a small text file that a server can automatically store on your computer and retrieve later. We instruct your browser to place a "cookie" into a file on your hard drive when you visit our site. Each time you return to the site, the cookie is re-sent to us so that we may track which of our services you use and what content you view (including advertisements). In addition, we collect the Internet Protocol address of each visitor to our site, which is a number that can be used to identify your internet service provider, among other things.

**_Use of Information_**

**ResellRightsMastery.com** may disclose information we have collected from you and/or content you have made available on our site in the following circumstances, and also may disclose such information and/or content to others when **ResellRightsMastery.com** believes in good faith that the law requires it, or to protect the rights or property of **ResellRightsMastery.com** or its visitors.

Upon request, **ResellRightsMastery.com** may disclose your contact information to customers of your website, government agencies, any trademark or copyright owner requiring to contact you in regards to transactions or content on your site.

Information submitted by you at the time of registration (including but not limited to your name and e-mail address) may be used but not limited to marketing and promotional purposes by **ResellRightsMastery.com**. 

This information may also be shared with other companies who offer a co-branded or rebranded versions of our site, who offer services in conjunction with **ResellRightsMastery.com** , or who are business partners of **ResellRightsMastery.com**. **ResellRightsMastery.com** will not otherwise identify you personally to other companies, or to any advertisers. **ResellRightsMastery.com** provides demographic information in aggregate form to advertisers on our site, without identifying any user personally. 

We may use information provided by you when you participate in contests or surveys on our site to send information about **ResellRightsMastery.com** to you, or to give information to advertisers in aggregate form.

**ResellRightsMastery.com** uses cookies to determine whether you are logged on to the site, to maintain your session, and to automatically log you out if your computer remains idle for a specified amount of time when using our service. We also use cookies to measure the traffic on our site, track which of our services you use, which content you view (including advertisements) and how long you view it. We collect IP addresses for administrative purposes (such as to help diagnose problems with our server) and to gather aggregate demographic information about our visitors. 

By using **ResellRightsMastery.com** and disclosing information to us you expressly consent to the uses described in this Privacy Statement.
